What should I do?
Hello.
- Do you have the break lever?
- I don't have the lever yet.
- It's going to take a week to get it.
- Okay. Then fix it when you get that.
Have it checked please.
- Did you buy another motorcycle again?
- No. That's not mine. It's hers.
You must be happy that your girlfriend
has the same hobby as yours.
Your skin looks older under the sunshine.
Your ugly face doesn't change at all.
I read a newspaper a few days ago.
There was a story about a woman who
killed a man because he called her ugly.
And the man was about 50 years old.
- So are you going to kill me?
- No.
Somebody is going to kill you even if it's
not me if you treat a woman like this.
I only do that to you.
I don't talk to women like this.
- I look so easy to you, don't I?
- I don't know. I feel so comfortable with you.
I'm not a rude man actually.
What are you two doing?
You're interrupting the conduct of business.
I was going to go inside.
Where are you going?
I'm trying to build one more
restaurant but there's so much to do.
- Besides, I got to do the engagement.
- Doing that is useless.
It's hard to find useful things
while preparing the wedding.
Bye guys.
Tell him to buy delicious food.
He never gives me anything for free.
I always have to pay him.
Is being a handsome guy everything?
He's not handsome. He looks like a player.
You look better than him.
There's no woman like Dong Bi.
How could she marry another man?
- I came to report a missing person.
- Are you a family member?
No, I'm her friend.
- How long has it been?
- It has been about a week.
Did her family get a call from her or something?
I don't know her family's phone number.
Can I search for it? She's from Busan.
You're her friend but you don't know their phone number?
Then she must've went to her house.
Can you use a tracking device to find where she is?
That way I can feel better.
We can only use that device
under certain conditions.
You should just call 911.
You need to be a family member, or bring
some sort of evidence that she was kidnapped.
Or you should know her identification
number and her address.
But you don't meet any of these conditions.
You're the only friend to me.
You're the only friend to me too.
Without you, I'd be a woman without a friend.
- Let's toast for our bright year of 2008!
- Cheers!
If you're on a trip, at least text
me that you're fine.
Otherwise, we're not friends anymore.
There's nobody I can talk to except for you.
Hae Yoon.
He's ignoring my calls again.
This reminds me of the old times.
I told you I'm sorry for slapping you.
You keep ignoring my calls and texts.
You did that when you broke up with me.
What people do when they break up with their
lover is who they really are! It's so true.
You're the same son of a bitch from the old times.
Sang Jin.
Hello.
You do know how to make me feel sorry.
I haven't been able to contact Dong Bi for days.
I went to the police to report a
disappearance but they didn't listen to me.
So?
Find her please. You're a lawyer.
There must be some policemen you know.
I'm going to meet my
friends to drink tonight.
So you can't? What's wrong with these people?
Why can't they take it seriously?
I can't contact her!
Then come to my office.
I'll finish it as soon as possible.
Hi. Dr. Nam is doing the surgery now.
Please wait.
- I'll wait at his office.
- Hey, hey.
What are you doing?
- Playing a game.
- I mean, why are you playing a game here?
- Who are you?
- Aren't you a model?
Have we met before?
No. People told me that.
This is our third time to see each other.
Dr. Nam, he's asking me what I'm doing and
he's not telling me who he is before he asked.
I need to talk to you for a moment.
What's wrong with you?
I'm too stunned to get mad at you.
I think you hate a woman who cries
and you hate a stupid woman even more.
So I changed the plan. What is it that you
can give to me if I break up with you?
Nothing. So this is how you
use your brain to look smart?
Yeah. This is all that I can.
So I was thinking that it's better to borrow
a smart brain before I get dumped by you.
I'm going to sue you for committing illicit
sexual acts under false promises of marriage.
- Why?
- Come here.
You got scared because I told you
I'm going to sue you, didn't you?
Let's just keep seeing each other.
I won't feel threatened by
you because you're stupid.
You didn't get scared?
It has been a long time
since that crime is gone.
- Is it gone?
- Just do what I tell you.
If you do that, I won't leave you.
I'm sorry for making you wait.
Let's go to a treatment room.
- I'm just going to go home.
- Why?
Who's that woman?
Is this what I'm thinking?
You can't say until you know it's 100% sure.
You're cheating with her, aren't you?
End it with her before others find out.
You don't understand because you
haven't lived up to my age.
Don't tell me you understand just
because you and I are men.
Morals are what we're supposed
to follow to be good people!
Hey, Sis.
- Did you get the gifts?
- Yeah.
Then why didn't you call me?
Am I supposed to call you first?
- I was going to.
- Then buy me dinner.
Then what about my husband's dinner?
You have a maid.
She will go home soon.
What's your daughter-in-law going to do about the gift?
We've decided not to do that kind of stuff.
People waste so much money on that.
We don't want to be one of them.
Then am I not going to get
any gift from you guys?
But my daughter-in-law sent you the gifts.
We're not getting anything from Hae Yoon.
How can she send you gifts?
You're married a man who
had no ambitions but only love.
And now your son and his wife
are doing the same thing.
You can probably work that out this time.
But it'd be hard to hang out with you
if it goes to the 3rd generation.
Did your husband stop cheating on you?
What we're looking for is different.
There isn't anything about you that I envy.
My husband and I still love each other so much.
Have you felt this warmth and love in your life?
You probably don't know because you're
doing the same thing our parents did.
That's the downside.
You know Hae Yoon's sister married a
married man and ruined the family, right?
And Hae Yoon is someone from that kind of family.
What I'm suffering for now is...
the cost of what I had done wrong in my previous life.
I'm on my way to see you. Please come.
You came early.
I can't hang out with people when
I know someone is waiting for me.
- Did you drink a lot?
- A glass of beer.
So what happened to Dong Bi?
Tell me about the last time you saw her
with every detail that you are certain of.
I was sitting across from her at this restaurant.
- And we talked.
- About what?
- I can't tell you.
- Then I can't make the right judgment.
There might be a clue in that conversation.
She might have gotten mad at you because of
the conversation and ignored your calls.
- That's not it. Leave that out.
- You want me to help you or not?
Anyway, the news was on TV and she
was gazing at it for a while.
What was the news about?
I couldn't hear it well because I
was sitting back against the TV.
Anyway, it was about somebody's death.
What date was it? If we searched
what was in the news on that day,
then we can find if it's
related with her disappearance.
What if it's not?
Then you'll have to tell me
what you guys talked about.
But you will soon. What's there to
be related with Dong Bi on the news?
Jung Hoon.
It's not a video chat. Get it.
- Hello?
- How's your cold?
I got better.
- What was that?
- What do you mean? I didn't hear anything.
- Where are you?
- I'm home.
- Then come out. I'm in front of your house.
- What?
The light in your room is turned off.
Are you with your mom?
No.
- Come out.
- Can we meet later?
I bought porridge.
I'll go home after I give it to you.
Please don't get mad.
What is it?
- I'm not home.
- Then where are you?
- I'm at Dong Bi's house.
- Why? Is she back?
No. I came to check if she's back.
Wait there. I'll go now.
- Shoot. I got to go.
- Let me give you a ride.
- You drank a beer.
- But it was only one glass.
- But still!
- Oh, my coat!
Oh my God! Everything will be over!
Let's give it a shot though.
What are you doing here?
- We see each other very often.
- What are you doing here?
I came to see Dong Bi.
I'm helping her business now.
But I haven't heard from her.
What about you?
Me too.
- Then let's go together.
- She's not here now.
You knew she's not here.
Then why did you come here?
Didn't you say you came to see her?
Would you like to drink with me?
Thank you.
Please understand Hae Yoon.
She has this habit of worrying about
things that are going to happen.
That's why she's overreacting
and that causes a problem.
I know that too.
What happened last time was part
of my responsibility. I'm sorry.
Are you saying sorry instead of her?
You're acting like you're already married to her.
Only the wedding is left.
Well, preparing for the wedding
is harder than it looks.
Especially, in this country, saving
one's face is very important.
Many couples break up because of that.
That's not going to happen to us.
There were many crises that we went
through while preparing for the wedding.
- But we overcame them well.
- Really?
I've done many divorce lawsuits.
Couples who fought a lot during
that process came to get a divorce.
So are you saying I'm going to
get a divorce or something?
- I'm not cursing you or something.
- I think you are.
If that's what you think, maybe it is.
People hear how they want to hear.
Maybe you want me to
think it's a curse.
Hang on.
This is Jun Sang Jin.
- How's your cold?
- It got better.
What was that?
I should get going now.
- Your ring tone is very unique.
- I have a unique taste on that.
- I see.
- Why?
Because I think I heard it somewhere before.
Then I'll see you later with Hae Yoon.
I don't think you will.
I'm not that cool.
I see. Then let's meet up with Dong Bi.
How can I not call you?
What's there to talk about with him anyway?
You're so mean. Aren't you supposed to say
thank you? You only care about him.
- Thank you.
- Sure, whatever.
What was I doing there anyway?
Why am I doing this to you?
I got to go.
Do you know who I just met?
- Who?
- Jun Sang Jin.
He came to see Dong Bi. Aren't you surprised?
It's like you knew about it already.
I'm usually calm and relaxed in any situation.
- By the way...
- What?
She would hate me if I ask why she lied to me, right?
Never mind.
Oh, anyway.
What is it?
I'm sure I heard IU's song when
I was on the phone with you.
- It's Sang Jin's ring tone.
I know it's impossible for you
to be with him at that time.
It was kind of creepy when
I heard his ring tone.
Did a ghost do a prank on
his phone or something?
If it's a ghost that did it,
it's a good sign.
People say if singers see a ghost at their
studio, there song will be a big hit.
Yeah. Then our wedding will be a big hit.
- Oh, I should call your father.
- You don't forget about anything.
- Hey, Son.
- Mr. Hae, it's Hae Yoon.
Hello.
Thank you for the wedding gifts.
I'm sorry
that I'm not a good daughter-in-law.
It's okay.
As much as you love me, I'll try not
to make you disappointed in me.
You don't have to do that.
Let's just be comfortable with each other.
- Okay, Mr. Hae.
- Alright.
It's not easy to make someone become my family.
It's good you didn't go to the hospital.
Why?
He wasn't kind.
Was Do Hyun not kind to you?
What are you doing?
Do you remember when I asked you
out after I got my first salary?
I think love is forever.
It's a person that changes, not love.
Love doesn't change.
Let's show the world that it's true.
Let's not do it here now.
It's Dong Bi's house.
Are you mad?
You are.
You're mad.
What are you doing?
A cleaning woman will do it.
- It's so dirty here. I'll just do it.
- That's so sweet of you.
I should raise your salary.
- Why did you come back?
- I forgot to take my car key.
- Hae Jin.
- Yes?
What did you say your dream is?
A hospital coordinator.
Doing nice things even if others don't
notice is a very good personality trait.
If you live like this, your dream will come true.
You dressed like a rich woman.
I almost didn't recognize you.
You look the same.
- Because my life hasn't changed.
- I'm getting a divorce by a lawsuit.
What's the reason for telling me that?
You told me that I'm suffering now
because it is the cost of...
And I also told you that you will have
a future full of suffering for sure.
I'm sorry.
- I don't want you to forgive me...
- Don't worry. I won't until I die.
I was so unstable and nervous
even when I was happy.
'Do I really deserve to enjoy this happiness?'
I feel better as if I wanted this to happen.
Your unhappiness is comforting me.
You're trying to win the lawsuit without
feeling guilty by apologizing to me?
I want to reset my life.
I couldn't apologize to you at that
time because I didn't know what to do.
I want to start over.
I think my suffering started
from hurting your feelings.
I've dated a married man too.
After I got a divorce, I became a
person that I really hated to become.
Life is so random.
You don't know what's going to happen.
It's just like there are colorful designs in life.
I should leave now.
I'm kind of happy to see you guys ended like that.
Hurt each other's feelings as much as you can.
And then you should win
because I hate him more.
I know the counteraction will be coming.
Since the money you have is a lot,
they'll ask for a big settlement.
I heard there are many judges that
are favorable to women these days.
Usually a woman judge is like that.
A divorce lawsuit is more
favorable for women usually.
Because people feel pity on
women when they get a divorce.
If it gets disadvantageous for me,
just bring up a compromise.
Yeah, I should.
There's bad news.
The judge for this case is a man
but he's favorable for women.
But Jung Hae Jin changed her lawyer.
I know him. He's very tenacious.
That's not good.
The good news is that I'm
more tenacious than he is.
They didn't come home yet.
Oh my God! When did she take that with her?
It's very dangerous for her!
The light is on.
Your sister must be home.
I can't go home now.
I'm going to go when she's asleep.
Is your sister that scary?
Just give it a shot!
She might be okay with that.
Okay! Give it a shot!
You're teaching a very good lesson!
- I've seen you before!
- Deul Ja.
You crazy bitch!
You made her ride that!
You tricked her to buy a motorcycle?
It's not that. I wanted to ride one.
Wait, are you...
I can't even speak now. You're the one
with the pan fried tofu, aren't you?
You gave him all the side dishes, didn't you?
Tell me.
- You had the tofu, didn't you?
- Yes, I did.
You come here.
You both are going to die tonight.
Are you crazy, huh?
Why do you date a man like him?
Deul Rae!
Get back here right now!
Get your face out of my way.
What the?
Wear this after you shower.
- Don't you have a woman size?
- You're not supposed to ask me that.
- You're trying to seduce me, aren't you?
- What?
You're pretending to be so
surprised like an innocent woman?
I can't really blame you now.
I should've prepared to listen to your nonsense.
Nonsense?
- Like this?
- Get that out of my sight.
Should I?
If you do that one more time,
I'm going to kiss you again.
It didn't mean anything.
I was playing with you.
She kissed me.
You came home late.
Hae Yoon got a cold so I was with her.
What a good husband you are.
Didn't Dad get a refund for those yet?
He did. Those are from Chae Young.
I knew this would happen so I was going to do it first.
Why did you leave them there?
Just to show you and make
you realize the reality.
She can't afford those.
Does she have to steal stuff then?
- She doesn't have money.
- Why are you yelling?
Not having enough money makes people
uncomfortable and intimidated.
I've become down at heel while preparing the wedding.
This is why I'm mad.
Why do you have to feel like that?
Hae Yoon must've felt this more
than I do but she's very confident.
Do you know how many times she
has controlled me while dating?
I even pretended to die because of her.
You fool.
Your son doesn't have ambitions.
He's just a salary man.
What I can earn is limited.
I should get used to that.
With Hae Yoon, I won't feel
intimidated even if I'm poor.
We have our values that we want to protect.
I'm not going to tell her about the wedding
gift. I don't want to hurt her feelings.
I hope you can do that.
You dweeb.
Blame Dad.
I think I must have gotten his genes.
You half-wit!
Thank you.
I wanted to let down my hair.
Who told you guys to tie my hair?
It's me.
- Why are you wearing shoes in the room?
- These are new. Mrs. Hae bought it for me.
You're a princess.
Fine feathers make fine birds.
Where are you going anyway?
Jung Hoon's cousin's engagement.
You shouldn't go to other people's
occasions after your wedding date is set.
Dong Bi said that too.
It's just a superstition.
Whether it is or not, you shouldn't go.
I have to go anyway. Don't say anything.
Do you know this bastard?
Who?
I think it's him. The one you
talked about when we were eating.
This bastard is close with that
bastard and got a divorce twice.
I know this bastard but that bastard is Do Hyun?
- Yeah.
- What about Min Ho?
Your aunt didn't come home after
she went out with Min Ho.
- Do you know where he lives?
- Do Hyun would know.
Don't keep calling his name.
What should I do about her?
Let her be. She probably has a plan.
Do you think a person with a plan would
ride a motorcycle? What if she gets hurt?
She's going to have to stay home forever.
Mom.
Then I'm the one who has to take care of her.
Don't say that easily just
because it's not your business.
Are you not going to yell at me?
No, I'm not. I'll help you.
Since you're helping him, help him eat
this too. He doesn't eat spinach.
This and this too.
You shouldn't eat only what you want.
Eat this too.
- I don't want to eat.
- Eat it!
Then you eat first.
You don't eat that either.
If you eat, I'll eat too.
Then don't eat. You don't have
to do what you don't want to.
I'm not going to eat.
- Then what are you going to do?
- Play a game.
Get here right now and finish your meal!
Even if you want to play a game, you should eat first.
Do you know you keep two tongues in one mouth?
Go play a game in your room. I'll get
you something to eat soon, okay?
- What are you doing?
- You think it's easy to take care of a kid?
You can't raise a kid. Forget about custody.
I know you're doing it to make me mad.
Do you know the goal of my life recently?
Not giving you anything that you want.
- What are you doing here?
- He's here now?
- You're here.
- Yeah. Hi, how are you?
I heard you got so many complaints about me.
Let's not talk about it.
I came to ask you something.
- You know Min Ho, don't you?
- Why?
Where does he live?
- Why do you want to know?
- You don't have to know that.
Just tell me where he lives.
I know it's not going to be good.
I can't tell you.
Fine. I'll tell you why.
That bastard kidnapped my sister!
Really?
Do you know how old she is?
She can't be kidnapped.
You're going to go there and tell him to take the
responsibility for her just like you did to me.
What?
You're such a crazy bastard.
If I had known what kind of person you
are, I wouldn't have made her marry you.
We would've just gotten some compensation.
I thought you were a great man
since your father was a doctor!
If I think of that time,
I want to poke my eyes!
Me too!
If I had known how rude you are,
I probably wouldn't have
married her either.
I cut my own throat!
You don't know where he lives?
Of course I don't.
Look at him. He doesn't even say good bye.
- Have a seat.
- I should go.
- Do you have a place to go?
- The kindergarten.
Just eat some. I made it for you.
I don't think it'd taste good.
I'm going to go.
Are you shy?
Is that why?
Shy for what?
- You can play me again. Please do that.
- Get that out of my sight.
You don't want to do that now?
Then tell me whenever you want to.
When I'm with you, I think I'm
becoming another person.
- In a good way?
- A bad way.
But I feel so good.
Who is it?
- It's Do Hyun.
- Oh my God!
- What's up?
- Want to ride a motorcycle?
I was going to eat...
What relationship are you
having with Deul Rae?
Why aren't you answering? What is it?
It's not like that.
The apron and the shoes
were Deul Rae's. Right?
Why do you have so many questions today?
Come out! I know you're here.
Come out!
I'm going to tell Deul Ja where you are.
3, 2, 1.
I'm here. Don't tell her.
Deul Rae, don't develop feelings for him.
He would never see you as a woman.
Don't think it's love because
he's being very nice to you.
He's nice to every woman.
He's just playing the fool with you.
I know. I was going to leave.
- Wait. Let me take you home.
- Stop playing with her.
Her feelings might get hurt.
Can you say that to her?
Did you hear that?
My feelings might get hurt.
So don't play the fool with me. I'd never
play the fool with you ever since I met you.
I'm afraid to show my feelings to others.
I'm afraid they'd leave me.
I'm not a great man but if I can live one
more time, I want to do that with you.
I'm not a great woman either so I don't
want to date someone that's not great.
Did you just get rejected by her?
Just leave the house.
You're a really bad man.
The worst thing for a man is to get
embarrassed in front of a woman.
- Why do you like her?
- She's a femme fatale.
He really likes her.
Mrs. Hae.
- Hi.
- You guys came early.
- You look beautiful.
- It's what she bought for me.
- Thank you.
- Sure. Let's go.
Let's go.
Now the groom and the bride
will exchange their rings.
Now the groom, Gong Ki Joong and the
bride, Han Chae Young will cut the cake.
Thank you very much. Let's toast
to a happy marriage.
Please lift the glass in front of you.
For the bride and groom, cheers!
The coffee isn't as good as the one Ki Joong makes.
He's probably engaged by now.
He's a betrayer. He said he would live with me.
- One of us is leaving now.
- The other one is coming.
Are you getting a divorce?
Hae Jin wants a divorce.
Apologize to her and tell her you
will transfer some properties to her.
- Then she will forgive you.
- Why didn't you do that?
Then they would live with me just
because of money. I'd hate that.
Then why do you want me
to do something you hate?
You got a kid. If you have a kid, you can't
only think about if you loved her or not.
I thought she would come back if I gave her some money.
But she sued me now.
- Please don't do that.
- Who doesn't know it's not good?
But I can't just sit there and do nothing.
Just let her do what she wants.
My marriage with my ex-wife was boring but
peaceful. I ruined it to marry Hae Jin.
Do you know how it feels to be betrayed?
How dare she does that to me?
- She's going to get paid for that.
- You're the one who's done wrong!
Give me that.
Wait for me.
Aunt Eun Kyung!
Doing an engagement ceremony
is so classy and nice.
Honey, we had our engagement
here too, didn't we?
Yeah, we did!
You look so beautiful. I like your dress.
- Thank you.
- Live a happy life.
You're going to hear it again at the wedding.
I think you're jealous. Why don't you
have them get engaged?
- Long time no see.
- Yeah.
Dong Bi really didn't come here.
She's irresponsible.
It's a good day.
Let's talk about good things.
Like what? For example, your apology to me was
just a show for your parents-in-law?
Let's go over there and meet people now.
Was that a show?
Why aren't you answering? If that's not
true, I'm going to go yell at her.
- How dare she said that in front of us?
- They're still young. We should understand.
No. Tell me. Is that true?
Yeah.
Don't laugh!
Why did you do that?
There isn't anything that I've done
wrong so I didn't want to apologize.
I'm mad that she made the problems bigger.
So you're just a normal woman.
I really liked how you
endured the unfairness for me.
To you, it was a petty trick?
I'm sorry.
What do you think of this bag?
For others, it's what I gave you as a wedding
gift but it's actually what Mr. Hae gave you.
No. It's what Chae Young
gave me as her wedding gift.
She sent this with a beautiful shawl.
We got a refund for the
one my husband bought.
Jung Hoon wanted this to be a secret
because it might hurt your feelings.
How did you make my son become like that?
I'm sorry.
I declared myself to be a mother-in-law who doesn't
get a wedding gift from
a daughter-in-law.
So now you don't have to prepare for the
wedding gift. Your petty tricks worked.
Didn't it?
How bad is your financial problem?
Your mother owns a store.
She said she's going to
do anything for her kids.
What is she going to do about her daughter's wedding?
Does she think a marriage is like a
business since she's doing the business?
Does she want to make a profit out of your marriage?
It's not the money that causes problems.
It's your mind!
Does she know about the wedding gift?
She doesn't know, does she?
Is my son getting married to an orphan?
Don't cry. If others see this,
they might think I'm the bad one.
People are walking by.
- How was the meal?
- The bread was good.
That's so your style.
Did you buy her those?
You're too kind.
- Let's get in.
- Okay.
Oh my God.
Sang Jin.
- What?
- What's wrong with your voice?
Because I'm in a bathroom.
I have something to tell you about Dong Bi.
It's up to you to come or not..
Let's meet.
I'll go get my car. Wait here.
You came home already?
She left.
- Mom, did you scold her a lot?
- Yeah. I even made her cry.
Why? Do you want to take her side?
- No. Good job.
- I know you don't mean that.
She has twisted thoughts.
I liked her because I
thought she was well-bred
going through hard times.
But I was wrong.
No, she doesn't have twisted thoughts.
Dong Bi is her best friend.
Chae Young started it by saying
how Dong Bi is irresponsible.
She's right though. Dong Bi was
supposed to work but she didn't come.
Did you forget that she dated Ki Joong before?
How could she come to the engagement?
Then why did she say she
would work for Chae Young?
Birds of a feather flock together.
Let's stop.
Who do you think loves you the most?
It's me. I can tell everyone that it's me.
Suck it up! Don't get
controlled by others, you fool!
I'm just going to get a taxi.
I'll call you later.
Isn't this Dong Bi?
I think it is.
It doesn't make sense.
Why did she live like a poor woman then?
She took so much money out of me.
- Do you know anything about this?
- No.
Maybe I wasn't a friend to her.
Jung Hoon.
- Did you guys fight?
- No.
Then why aren't you answering it?
Because I don't want to.
Home.
I wish when I open my eyes,
my wedding is done.
Then you'd feel relieved that all the
problems you're having are gone?
The problems you're having is just the beginning.
It's like a prep-test. You know you should do
well on a prep-test to do well on a real test.
Don't you regret that you called off
your marriage right before the wedding?
We had a fight every
single day while preparing
for the wedding. We hurt
each other's feelings.
Besides, her father is also my boss.
He was very stubborn. I probably
could endure today but not tomorrow.
I can't take a road when I
know what's going to happen.
If I take the road?
You will be like your sister or give
up everything and drink everyday.
You're so mean. How could you
talk about my sister like that so easily?
Why not? You can't do that easily
because you're embarrassed.
I can't organize my thoughts yet.
I don't know what to do.
Should I go to Do Hyun and use violence?
Don't do that. I think your
mother did that already.
Yeah, you're right.
She must be a hard one. One of the
reasons for the divorce was her.
You probably know everything about my family.
I can't even hide things in front of you.
Do you know how many things
I'm hiding to my fiance?
I feel so bad.
I don't think you should reveal
everything to your fiance.
Thinking like that is just a fantasy.
People can even hide things to themselves.
You should hide things if you can cover
so he doesn't have to be bothered.
- You look so mature.
- So don't be rude to me.
You can rely on me if
you're having hard times.
I'm doing this because of the nice things
you've done for me when we dated.
You're bothering me.
What did I do?
You embarrassed me in front
of people a while ago.
You hold grudges so much.
You made people embarrassed first.
I hate when the mood gets embarrassed
just because of one person.
Why should I have a marriage without
love if I can't do anything that I want?
I spanked him for the first time.
He was so precious to me that
I didn't even hit him at all.
It was like my heart breaking.
You find out violence isn't a
good thing after you used it?
But he doesn't care if I'm mad or heart
broken because he's crazy about Hae Yoon.
I should do something about that.
Then what are you going to do?
I think I should fish for
what I want from now on.
I hate to say this but
one's heart follows money.
Hae Yoon's mother doesn't want
to spend a penny on my son.
I guess how she treated him at the
meeting is how she treats him now.
How did she treat him at the meeting?
She was late at the meeting and she said
he's just a regular salary man.
Hae Yoon had many chances to meet better
men but since Hae Yoon likes him,
she approved this marriage.
- Do you remember all this?
- How can I not? It's about my son.
I can't let this happen again.
I'll get a taxi when I'm done.
You can go home first.
I'll drink some tea while I wait.
Call me when you're done.
- Hi.
- Come here.
- Okay.
- Have a seat.
- Thanks.
I was kind of neglecting my store
so I had to ask you to come here.
It's okay.
Would you like to drink some coffee?
It's okay. I drank it before I came.
Don't worry.
How much is the rent for this place?
Why do you ask? Are you going to pay for it?
It's not that much.
So how much is it?
Why did you want to see me?
You want me to help you with Hae
Yoon and Joon Hoon's house right?
- Yeah, I do.
- I'll help you.
How much money are you willing to spend on that?
I need to see the house to figure that out.
Oh, you didn't see the house yet.
I'll show you that soon.
Then how much are you willing to
pay for your daughter's wedding?
Why do you keep asking about money?
Getting our kids married is
something we should do together.
It has been one sided until now.
You can't do the same amount as I do.
You're the groom's side.
I know parents of the groom
should pay more.
I guess there's nothing I can do. If
you want us to pay, we'll have to.
If you want us to buy the house and pay
for the wedding hall, then we should.
What is she trying to do?
Of course there aren't many people who don't
do that but since you have a money problem,
we should do that.
Yeah, you're right.
But if you try, you can fit
our plan to suit others.
You can raise your standard. I
think you're sparing bones too much.
This bag is what I got from my nephew's wife.
Would you like to get a brand
named bag as a wedding gift?
I told Hae Yoon not to do the wedding gift.
Then all we have left is buying
furniture for the house.
You said you wanted me to help
you with that stuff last time.
Since the kids are busy working. How
about you take a look at the house and
give me the estimated amount of money?
I'll decorate their house with that.
You care about your kids very much.
So you probably want to buy nice
stuff for their first house.
It's the mother who loves the son-in-law.
Care about him too not just
your first son-in-law.
- Sure.
- Then I'll see you later.
How are you going home? It'll cost
you a lot if you take a taxi here.
Bye.
Some women have it all, and some women
don't have anything.
I won't feel small because of that.
The plaintiff, Nam Do Hyun, wants a divorce?
Yes.
Are you not going to change your mind?
You've lived with her as
husband and wife for years.
I'm not going to.
The defendant, Jung Hae Jin,
do you want a divorce?
Yes.
- Do you not want to change your mind?
- No.
There's a different view on division
of property and compensation.
- Does the defendant plan to submit evidence?
- Yes.
In order to prove the affair,
I'd like to request his call history.
And to find out his properties, I'd like to
request financial transactions and income tax.
Is the plaintiff planning to submit the evidence?
To prove her overspending, I'd request
detailed statement of her card.
Then I'll set up the date again
after you submit the evidence.
Rise.
Nice to see you again.
We might be friends if we see
each other one more time.
- Be easy on us.
- That's what I wanted to tell you.
So he's the new lawyer?
Hi, I'm Jun Sang Jin.
Contact me when you need me.
- I'm specialized in divorce cases.
- You're kind of brazen.
Not as much as you are.
I'll see you at home.
I'm not going to make food for you anymore.
Eat it at Yuri's house.
So you can take a picture
of me as the evidence?
Feel free to go. I already have
enough pictures for the evidence.
Yeah, feel free to go.
We're debating which pictures we should
use as evidence. There are so many.
It can't be one sided.
There's a lot of evidence to
prove your overspending.
Women who overspend usually
ruin their family.
It's not referring to you, Hae Jin.
If it's not referring to her, then what
you said before becomes useless.
You make money by saying useless stuff. I'm so jealous.
She's going to have to pay for a contingent fee anyway.
It must be tough.
No, it's not. I'll pay her with the money that I will get from your property.
- It's all your money.
- Let's stop it here.
He's still your husband in a document.
Let's go easy on him for now. Let's go.
I met your mother.
Do you also think this marriage is your loss?
- Drink some tea.
- You can just tell me.
I think a man and a woman are different.
It's different from how they look.
What a man can do and what a woman can do are also different.
A house that a husband and a wife live should be provided by the groom's side.
You can't change that in one day.
She took the credit herself for buying the house.
And now she starts to interfere about furniture for the house.
I can't even breath.
She wants me to give her the budget.
Is this a congress or something?
She said she will do the execution of the budget.
Have you heard of a mother-in-law decorating a marital home?
I'll talk about that with my mom.
Don't just talk with her. You should do something about this!
You're not a man if you can't protect your woman!
- Mrs. Jung.
- What?
- Can I be honest with you today?
- Sure!
I don't think you should talk about this with me.
Then who should I talk with?
I think you should talk about this with nobody.
Are you speaking with a serious face in front of me?
Yes, I am speaking with a serious face.
I can't make a funny face in front of you.
- Are you dissatisfied with me?
- Yes, I am.